<?xml version="1.0"?>
<PrivacyPolicy>
	<bodycontent>
		<![CDATA[
			<p>
				<b>Brick, Inc.</b> has created this privacy statement 
				in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The 
				following discloses our information gathering and dissemination 
				practices for this website.
				<br/>
				<br/>
				This site uses cookies to keep track of your login name and recipe 
				search preferences. Functionality within the site will not work 
				properly if your browser does not accept cookies.
				<br/>
				<br/>
				The registration forms require you to give us contact information 
				(like your name and email address) and optional demographic 
				information (like your gender). We use your contact information to 
				send you information about our website. The contact information 
				is also used to contact you when necessary to resolve a service-
				related problem. You may opt-out of receiving future e-mail; see 
				the choice/opt-out section below.
				<br/>
				<br/>
				Personal profile data like your cookbook and dietary preferences 
				is also collected. We use this data to tailor your experience at our 
				site by showing you recipes according to your stated 
				preferences and store it for your benefit on future visits. The 
				personally identifiable parts of this information are not shared with 
				any outside party. Non-identifying demographic and profile 
				information, however, is shared with advertisers, business 
				partners and investors on an aggregate basis.
				<br/>
				<br/>
				<b>Choice/Opt-Out</b>
				<br/>
				Brick, Inc. provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving 
				communications from us at the point where we request 
				registration information. You can change this preference at any 
				time by selecting "preferences" and then clicking on "general info" 
				after providing your user name and password. If you would like to 
				remove your information from our database, e-mail this request to 
				<a href="mailto:optout@trybrick.com">optout@trybrick.com</a>.
				<br/>
				<br/>
				<b>Correct/Update</b>
				<br/>
				This site gives you the following options for correcting and 
				updating information previously provided.
				<br/>
				<ol>
					<li>
						For registration or personal profile information, select 
						"preferences" and then click on "general info" (after 
						entering your user name and password).
					</li>
					<li>
						Email <a href="mailto:optout@trybrick.com">optout@trybrick.com</a>.
					</li>
					<li>
						Send mail to the following postal address:
						<ul style="list-style-type:none">
							<li>Brick, Inc.</li>
							<li>200 Lumber Exchange Building</li>
							<li>10 South Fifth Street</li>
							<li>Minneapolis, MN 55402</li>
							<li>Attn: Customer Service</li>
						</ul>
					</li>
				</ol>
				<b>Changes in Use of Personally Identifiable Information</b>
				<br/>
				If Brick, Inc. decides to change how it uses the personally identifiable 
				information it collects from users, the changes will be highlighted 
				in this privacy statement and prior consent via e-mail will be 
				obtained from users who have previously provided information. 
				<br/>
				<br/>
				<b>Contacting the Web Site</b><br/>
				If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the 
				practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can 
				contact: 
				<br/>
				<ul style="list-style-type:none">
					<li>Brick, Inc.</li>
					<li>200 Lumber Exchange Building</li>
					<li>10 South Fifth Street</li>
					<li>Minneapolis, MN 55402</li>
					<li><a href="mailto:optout@trybrick.com">optout@trybrick.com</a></li>
				</ul>
			</p>
		]]>
	</bodycontent>
</PrivacyPolicy>